游戏音乐
[VIDEO GAME MUSIC]
Polycast 的观众朋友们  请看这里
Hey there, Polycasters.
Rob 在这里会宣布一个特殊的事情  因为就在今天
Rob here with a very special announcement because today,
我们进步了
we are moving.
好吧  不是今天  因为你们是在
Well, not today, because you're watching us
谷歌开发者频道收看的  下一集的Polycast
on the Google Developers channel, but the next episode of "Polycast"
将以全新的方式展现给大家
is going to be premiering on our brand-new,
将在 Chrome 开发者频道发布
revamped Chrome Developers channel.
也就意味着你可以给频道提交信息
That means you can subscribe to that channel
并获得你想要的通知和提示
and get notifications for the kinds of shows you like,
关于web的信息
shows about the web.
和 Polycast 一起  我们将
Along with "Polycast," we're going
向英国的合作伙伴靠拢
to be moving our British counterparts,
如 HTTP 203 和 Totally Tooling Tips
"HTTP 203" and "Totally Tooling Tips."
当我们创建新的节目时  我们也会在那个频道进行发布
As we create new shows, we'll be premiering them on that channel
as well.
因此请您单击批注进行查看
So click this annotation to check it out,
告诉你的朋友  分享出去
tell your friends, spread the word,
我希望能在 Chrome 开发者里面见到你
and I'll see you on Chrome Developers.
游戏音乐
[VIDEO GAME MUSIC]